(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Strawberry & Milk
Choco
Black choco Christmas!
Yuzuki Choco 5th Anniversary LIVE!
重大告知あり！
Important Announcement!
Sickbay Mistake
作詞：藤村鼓乃美(Hifumi,inc.)
Lyrics: Konomi Fujimura (Hifumi, inc.)
作曲・編曲：グシミヤギヒデユキ(Hifumi,inc.)
Composition & Arrangement: Hideyuki Gushimiyagi (Hifumi, inc.)
あー！
Ah!
ピンク色　ココア　淡い日差し
Pink-colored cocoa, faint sunlight
カーテンが揺れる　君の声
The curtains sway, your voice
近づく足音だけですぐ分かる
I can tell immediately just by the sound of approaching footsteps
今日はどんな味が欲しい？
What flavor do you want today?
ささやかクマの誘惑　U want it?
A modest bear's temptation. You want it?
Sickbay で待ち合わせ　密かな予感
Meeting up at the sickbay, a secret premonition
扉あけて　さあこちらおいで
Open the door and come over here
教科書に載っていない　この気持ちは何ですか？
What is this feeling that's not in the textbooks?
可愛い　可愛い　顔見せて
Show me your cute, cute face
Sickbay で会いましょう　魅了しちゃう
Let's meet at the sickbay, I'll charm you
永遠に続き　時間よ止まって
Continue forever, time stop
女子には見せられない　笑顔の秘密は
The secret of the smile I can't show to other girls is
甘い　甘い　お菓子あげる
I'll give you sweet, sweet treats
ささやかクマの誘惑　Ah ah ah
A modest bear's temptation. Ah ah ah
秒針のリズムを追い越していく
Overtaking the rhythm of the second hand
聞かせて　もっと君のこと
Tell me more about yourself
触れる指先で奏でるチューン
A tune played by touching fingertips
騒ぎだす鼓動　鳴り響くわ
My throbbing heart is echoing
もう後には戻れない
There's no turning back now
目配せ、鼻歌、上目遣い、見つめ合って
A wink, a hum, an upward glance, looking at each other
永遠の楽園に咲く　甘美な言葉
Sweet words blooming in the eternal paradise
耳元で囁いてあげる
I'll whisper in your ear
Sickbay で待ってるわ　密かな時間
I'll be waiting in the sickbay, a secret time
扉しめて　もっと近づいて
Close the door and come closer
神様も止められない　この気持ちの正体
The true nature of this feeling even God can't stop
知らないふりは　もうできない
I can't pretend not to know anymore
Sickbay で会いたいの　魅了しましょう
I want to see you in the sickbay, let's charm each other
永遠はここにあるって信じて
Believe that eternity is here
君にしか見せられない　笑顔の裏側は
The other side of the smile I can only show you is
甘い　甘い　果実あげる
I'll give you sweet, sweet fruit
ささやかクマの誘惑　もっとピカピカ
A modest bear's temptation, more sparkling
いつでもここで待ってる　My chocolate
I'll always be waiting here, my chocolate
今日は来てくれてありがとうー！
Thank you for coming today!
今回はブラッククリスマスということで...
This time, it's a Black Christmas...
まあね、ハロウィンとクリスマス、
Well, you see, Halloween and Christmas,
両方いっぺんに楽しんじゃおうという内容になっておりまーす！
we're going to enjoy both at once in this show!
ハッシュタグはこちら！
The hashtag is here!
カタカナで『ブラ』、
In katakana, "Bura",
そしてひらがなで『ちょこ』
and in hiragana, "Choco".
合わせて #ブラちょこ でいっぱい呟いてくださーい！
Together, that's #BuraChoco, so please tweet a lot!
それでは、早速次の曲にいきたいんですけど...
Now, I'd like to go to the next song right away...
まあね、ブラッククリスマスということで...
Well, since it's a Black Christmas...
みんなにね、ちょっとプレゼント
I've prepared a little present
用意しちゃいましたー！
for everyone!
それでは、こちらどうぞ！
Now then, here you go!
ドドーン！
Ta-da!
さてさて、中には何が入っているのかな？
Now, now, what could be inside?
みんな、楽しみにしててねー！
Everyone, look forward to it!
ブラッククリスマス / 作詞・作曲・編曲：まふまふ
Black Christmas / Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Mafumafu
ブッシュドノエルに蜘蛛の巣(リース)
Bûche de Noël with spider webs (wreaths)
Ding Dong Ding Dong
食べ足りないや
I haven't eaten enough
靴下の中身は味気ない
The contents of the stocking are bland
Ding Dong Ding Dong
響け鐘の音
Let the bells ring
いい子は嫌 あいつに任せた
I don't want to be a good kid; I'll leave that to them
悪い子になった あの子に夢中さ
I'm crazy about that girl who's become a bad kid
どこへ行くんだい？
Where are you going?
どこへ逃げるんだい？
Where are you running off to?
遊ぼう 遊ぼう
Let's play, let's play
For my for you Merry Christmas Gift
Our Santa Claus is coming tonight
Our Santa Claus...
悪い子はここかな？
Is the bad child here?
うなされるだけの毎日に
In days filled only with nightmares
まだ夢を見てるのはどうして
Why am I still dreaming?
12時の君を目覚めさせるよ
I'll wake you up at 12 o'clock
冷たい街角はChristmas
The cold street corners are Christmas
悪戯つきのセカイを
Looking for a world full of mischief,
探せる祈りなどはないさ
there are no prayers to be found
泣き声をかき消して鐘が鳴る
Bells ring, drowning out the cries
まだファンタジーを赤裸々に乗せての
Still carrying fantasy candidly,
今宵は Ding Dong Ding Dong
Tonight is Ding Dong Ding Dong
明かさず眠る Happy Christmas Day
Sleeping without dawn, Happy Christmas Day
愛のベール クリスマスにパーティ
A veil of love, a party at Christmas
賛成さオーケー チケットなしならば
I agree, okay, if there's no ticket
響けブラックな星の鐘ベルだ
Let the black star-bell ring
だからビフォアタイムだホワイト
So it's before time, white
導いたらハロウィン
If it leads to Halloween
それじゃなんだかんだで誰かの手のひら
Then somehow, it's in someone's palm
悪戯しようぜ
Let's play a trick
大騒ぎしようぜ
Let's make a big scene
偽物になって 本物気取って
Becoming a fake, pretending to be the real thing
どこへ行くんだい？
Where are you going?
どこへ逃げるんだい？
Where are you running off to?
遊ぼう There’s no way you can get out of this world
Let's play, there’s no way you can get out of this world
踊り明かせ今宵はトゥナイト
Dance the night away, tonight's the night
目眩めくばかりはサティスライト
Only dazzling things are satis-light
プラスな愛に嘘はない
There's no lie in positive love
ここに縛りはない
There are no restraints here
昨日2時から地獄まで
From yesterday at 2 o'clock until hell
いいからさっさと昇華しろ
Whatever, just hurry up and sublimate
Merry Christmas!
Our Santa Claus is coming tonight
Our Santa Claus...
攫ってやろうか？
Shall I snatch you away?
愛おしい幸せなんて
Something like precious happiness...
ジングルベルより 甘いマスター
A master sweeter than jingle bells
反り染めの指 君で踊ろう
Let's dance with your dyed fingers
終わらない悪夢を クリスマス
An endless nightmare, Christmas
傷つくだけの世界を
A world that only hurts
探すのは黒いサンタクロース
Seeking a black Santa Claus
泣き声をかき消して 鐘が鳴る
Drowning out the cries, the bell rings
まだ冷ややかな毒に乗せて
Still riding on a chilly poison
こびりついた愛も不安も
Clinging love and anxiety too
何だって委ねてごらん
Try entrusting everything
今宵はディンドン ディンドン 明かさず
Tonight is Ding-Dong, Ding-Dong, without dawn
眠るハッピークリスマスへ
To a sleeping Happy Christmas
Happy Halloween
作詞・作曲・編曲：Junky
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Junky
ねえ もう暗くなりそうだから
Hey, it's about to get dark
出ちゃってもいいかしら
So maybe it's okay to go out?
ちょっとね 魔法にかけられた
A little bit, cast under a spell...
君のお菓子から食べちゃうぞ
I'll start by eating your sweets!
きっと もう霧が濃くなるから
Surely, the fog will get thicker soon
みんな集まるかな
I wonder if everyone will gather
じっとして 甘いもの我慢した
Staying still, I held back on sweets...
ご褒美を ほら
Look, here's the reward
ひとつ ふたつ 鐘の音
One, two, the sound of the bell
騒ぎ出した 小さいお化けたち
The little ghosts have started a ruckus
今日は許してくれるのさ
Today, they'll forgive us
街に行こう
Let's go to the city
だって Happy Halloween
Because it's a Happy Halloween
いたずらしちゃうぞ ding-dong-dang
We're going to play tricks, ding-dong-dang
あっちもこっちも trick or treat
Here and there, trick or treat
キャンディーはくれないの？
Won't you give me some candy?
だって Happy Halloween
Because it's a Happy Halloween
いたいけなランタンパンプキン
Sweet little lantern pumpkins
疲れたジャックも踊るよ 朝まで
Even tired Jack will dance until morning
だって Happy Halloween
Because it's a Happy Halloween
お化けのカボチャもラララ
The ghost pumpkins too, la-la-la
今日は街中 trick or treat
Today, the whole town is trick or treat
チョコも頂戴よ
Give me some chocolate too
だって Happy Halloween
Because it's a Happy Halloween
不思議な世界へようこそ
Welcome to a mysterious world
疲れたジャックも歌うよ let's trick or treat
Even tired Jack will sing, let's trick or treat
もっと もっと 欲しい
I want more and more
欲張りなゴースト
Greedy ghosts
もうない？ それなら
No more? In that case...
いたずらの餌食ね
You're a victim of our tricks
くれない家なんて
A house that won't give anything...
庭木にトイレットペーパー ぐるぐるしちゃえ
Let's wrap toilet paper all around the garden trees
今夜はランタン灯してるなら
If the lanterns are lit tonight...
甘いの頂戴 さあ let's party night
Give us something sweet, now let's party night!
ほら だって Happy Halloween
Look, because it's a Happy Halloween
時計も回る tick-tack
The clock is turning, tick-tack
あっちもこっちも trick or treat
Here and there, trick or treat
目眩むパンプキンパイ
Dazzling pumpkin pie
だって Happy Halloween
Because it's a Happy Halloween
After all, it's Happy Halloween
だって Happy Halloween
今日は Happy Halloween
Today is Happy Halloween
さぁ Let's trick or treat
Now, let's trick or treat
赤いキャンディ 転がして
Rolling around a red candy
朝まで寝たくない！
I don't want to sleep until morning!
HAPPY SCARY HALLOWEEN
迷い込んだ？ バット、ハツラ、ポップの尻尾でも追ってついてきたのか？
Did you follow me in, chasing after the tail of a stray pop bat?
巻き戻った今日は蘇るのさ そら HAPPY SCARY NIGHT
Rewound, today is resurrected. Look, it's a HAPPY SCARY NIGHT.
そうさパンプキン 有象無象なら とびきりのショータイムへご招待
That's right, Pumpkin. For you rabble, I'll invite you to an extra special showtime.
君はきっともう帰れなくなる 後ろにご用心
You surely won't be able to return anymore. Watch your back.
甘い香りの方へ
Towards the sweet scent...
(まだまだ足りない)
(It's still not enough...)
ふわチョコ 欲張るの
Fluffy Choco is getting greedy...
(モンスター狙って 牙光らせるよ)
(Monsters are aiming and baring their fangs.)
お腹が空いたなら
If you're hungry...
(あら、無駄なの？)
(Oh, is it no use?)
お菓子がないなんて言わせない Trick or Treat
I won't let you say you have no candy. Trick or Treat.
Wow... HAPPY SCARY HALLOWEEN
Wow... イタズラし放題
Wow... All-you-can-prank
Wow... HAPPY SCARY HALLOWEEN
朝まで踊り明かせ Party Night
Dance until the morning, Party Night
さぁ一つになって歌おう 触ればジャックしたこの街で
Now, let's sing as one. In this town that we've hijacked if you touch it.
くり抜いた心満たすのさ そら HAPPY SCARY NIGHT
Filling the hollowed-out heart. Look, it's a HAPPY SCARY NIGHT.
生きてるもの そうじゃないもの 私達には関係ないのさ
Whether living or not, it doesn't matter to us.
神様にだって許されたなら 我らは自由
Since even God has forgiven us, we are free.
ほらこっちだよ
Look, it's this way.
(そっちじゃないよ)
(It's not that way.)
逃げていいよ
You can run away.
(怖がっていいよ その顔こそがご褒美さ)
(You can be afraid. That face is my reward.)
帰り道はない
There's no way back.
(朝が来るまで)
(Until the morning comes.)
楽しいパーティーは終わらない
This fun party never ends.
もうすぐ夜が明ける
The night will break soon.
(人も街も今に目を覚ます)
(People and the town will wake up soon.)
いずれまた訪れる夜まで
Until the night that will eventually return...
(この日を心に刻もう)
(Let's carve this day into our hearts.)
Happy Halloween なんてさ
Things like 'Happy Halloween'...
(もう明日にはみんな忘れて)
(Everyone will forget by tomorrow.)
聖なる夜へと向かうんだろう
They'll head towards the holy night.
(眠る前にもう一度だけ)
(Just once more before sleeping...)
Wow... HAPPY SCARY HALLOWEEN
Wow... まだ足りないんだぜ
Wow... It's still not enough.
Wow... HAPPY SCARY HALLOWEEN
我らの一度きりの Party Night
Our once-in-a-lifetime Party Night
Wow... HAPPY SCARY HALLOWEEN
Wow... イタズラし放題
Wow... All-you-can-prank
Wow... HAPPY SCARY HALLOWEEN
朝まで踊り明かせ Party Night
Dance until the morning, Party Night
ハロウィンナイトパーティ
Halloween Night Party
Trick or Treat カボチャの面 お化けたちがやってくる
Trick or Treat, pumpkin masks. The ghosts are coming.
少々、少々の家の前 お腹空かせたオオカミ
In front of a tiny, tiny house, a hungry wolf.
Trick or Treat ねぇお嬢さん 甘い香りきっとこれはそうだ
Trick or Treat, hey miss. This sweet scent is surely that.
お菓子をくださいな それかお嬢さん
Please give me some candy. Or maybe you, miss.
紅茶のパーティに
For the tea party...
パンケーキ
Pancakes!
上手に焼けました
They're cooked perfectly!
ピンチまずいっ！ともう焦っても
In a pinch, it's bad! Even if I panic now...
待ちくたびれて私が全部食べちゃった
Tired of waiting, I ate them all.
HALLOWEEN NIGHT PARTY 今宵はお化けが主役さ
HALLOWEEN NIGHT PARTY, tonight the ghosts are the stars.
お菓子をくれなきゃ襲っちゃうぞ
If you don't give me candy, I'll attack you!
HALLOWEEN NIGHT PARTY 今宵は踊り狂おうぜ
HALLOWEEN NIGHT PARTY, let's dance like crazy tonight.
道しるべはここだね ほら
The guidepost is right here, see?
...la la la la la...
Jack-o'-Lantern
術中は 私達も 複雑な処がまだ痛いの
During the procedure, even we still feel pain in complex places.
パッパと 生にいつも 取り込められていた
Quickly, we were always being drawn into life.
ぬるい美酒との 誘惑祭
An invitation to a lukewarm fine liquor festival.
皆で祝いましょう
Let's celebrate together.
家族も皆 揃ってる
All our family members are here.
骸骨は唄う
The skeletons are singing.
満月が照らす銀の抄
The full moon illuminates the silver manuscript.
Halloween Night Party 今宵はお化けが主役さ
Halloween Night Party, tonight ghosts are the stars.
シャンパン・ラン・タン・ラン・パン・イ・エ・イ！
Champagne lantern pan! Yay!
Halloween Night Party 今宵は踊り明かそうぜ
Halloween Night Party, let's dance the night away.
Mummy と Tequila ホッテッテ la la la la la
Mummy and Tequila, it's hot... la la la la la
Jack-o'-Lantern
空があくるから 闇の呪文は解けていく
Since the sky is brightening, the dark spells are dissolving.
Halloween Night Party 帰らなきゃいけない時間だ
Halloween Night Party, it's time we must head home.
来年もこの場所で会おう
Let's meet here again next year.
Halloween Night Party 今宵はお化けが主役さ
Halloween Night Party, tonight ghosts are the stars.
お菓子をくれなきゃ襲っちゃえ！
If you don't give us treats, we'll attack you!
Halloween Night Party 今宵は踊り狂おうぜ
Halloween Night Party, tonight let's dance like crazy.
Witch と 焦がれた筈で la la la la la
With a witch and the heat of the moment... la la la la la
Jack-o'-Lantern
Mrs. Pumpkinの滑稽な夢
Mrs. Pumpkin's Comical Dream
百から咲いた 触れ行く似顔んですかい
Is it a portrait bloomed from a hundred that's being touched?
何処へ行こうか 愉快に泣いた歌
Where shall we go? A song that cried out cheerfully.
ジャックは笑った 異な感情置いといて
Jack laughed, putting aside his strange emotions.
チョコレート頂戴 卑せに泣いた歌
Give me chocolate. A song that cried out in misery.
案山子がふらり
The scarecrow wandered
むせんで揺れた
and swayed in the fog.
食わず嫌いは カボチャのパイ
Picky eater's pumpkin pie.
レララ ルララ 私と踊ろうか
Lelala lulala, shall we dance?
まだ眠る お月様
The moon is still sleeping.
ほら 紡ぎは何処にもなくなった
Look, the spinning is gone everywhere.
つまらないや レララ ハッピーデイ
How boring. Lelala happy day.
でっち上げられた 魔法に敏感テトト
Concocted and sensitive to magic, tetoto.
魔女は焦がした 晦冥なようだった
The witch was scorched, it seemed like darkness.
ジャックは気取った 卑猥な感情持っといて
Jack put on airs, keeping his obscene emotions.
まんまるへ咲いた 腐乱なようだった
Bloomed into a circle, it seemed like rot.
厭きが並みか 企んだ
Is it the boredom of the waves? I've plotted.
電車を待つ
Waiting for the train.
手を繋いだ すま、許された
Holding hands, sorry, I'm forgiven.
巡りつく 果物の中
Arriving at the destination, inside the fruit.
ほら 束縛、不乱な...
Look, restraint, disorder...
...の中 まだ眠る お月様
...the moon is still asleep.
ミセス・パンプキン お迎えに上がりました
Mrs. Pumpkin, I've come to pick you up.
この夜はいつの間に 夢を壊したのだろう
When did this night break the dream?
あぁーーー
Aaah...
またここでおどけていたいのよ 夢のようなさくらんぼ
I want to keep playing the fool here, like a dream-like cherry.
ほら 吐き出した街灯が灯る ダンパッパ
Look, the vomited streetlights are lit, Dan-pa-pa.
ララルラル
La-la-ru-la-ru
私と踊りませんか 返事なんて来るはずもない
Won't you dance with me? There's no way an answer will come.
ほら 棺もどこにもなくなった つまらないや
Look, the coffin is gone too, it's boring.
沈み込んだ 泥の中
In the sunken mud
朝を待った 藪の中
In the thicket, waiting for morning
電車の中
In the train
ミセス・パンプキン
Mrs. Pumpkin
はーい！ということで 癒月ちょこ5周年ライブ ありがとうございます！
Hi! So, thank you so much for my 5th-anniversary live!
まあ5周年ということでね ちょっととある2人を呼んでね ご褒美もらっちゃおうかなーということで
Well, since it's my 5th anniversary, I thought I'd invite two guests and get a reward from them.
ちょこにご褒美タイムください！
Please give Choco a reward!
それでは早速呼んでいきましょう スバル！ルーナ！
Then let's call them right away. Subaru! Luna!
わー！ うなー！ おめでちゅう！
Yay! Una! Congratulations!
ちょこセンおめでちゅう！ おめでちゅうなななーい！
Choco-sen, congratulations! Congratulations, nora-na-na!
なんだかご褒美が欲しいようですねー
It sounds like you want a reward.
な、なのら？
N-Nora?
いや ちょこ5周年なんすよ
Well, it's my 5th anniversary.
それはマジでめでてぇ
That's truly worth celebrating.
いや めでたいでしょ
Right? It is.
何が欲しいんだ？ 言ってみろ！
What do you want? Tell us!
え、いいの？
Oh, can I?
やばい 嫌な予感する めっちゃ
Oh no, I have a really bad feeling about this.
いや もう最近2人のてぇてぇが足りてないと思って
Lately, I feel like I haven't seen enough wholesome moments from you two.
十分やってるじゃん！
We've been doing plenty!
いやいや足りないって！
No, no, it's not enough!
えー？ そうか？ ルーナどう思う？
Eh? Really? Luna, what do you think?
あー でもまあ5周年ってことだしね ちょこ先生にはお世話になってますし
Ah, but well, it is the 5th anniversary, and Choco-sensei has done a lot for us.
でしょ？ てぇてぇ てぇてぇ！
Right? Wholesome moments, wholesome moments!
激甘じゃん！
You're being way too soft!
てぇてぇ見せてやるか
Shall we show her some?
しょうがねぇな てぇてぇしてやるか
Can't be helped then. Let's be wholesome.
それじゃあ てぇてぇ師匠 姫森ルーナさん よろしくお願いします
Then, Wholesome Master Himemori Luna, please lead the way.
じゃあまずは一の型からいきますか
Then, shall we start with the first form?
一の型って何！？
What's the first form!?
初めて聞きました それ
That's the first I've heard of it.
新しすぎる！
That's too new!
それは ちゅう
It's a kiss.
いやそれもうさ クライマックスの型じゃん！
Wait, isn't that already the climax form!?
ちゅう！
Kiss!
え、2人がちゅうするってこと！？
Eh, you two are going to kiss!?
いやそれしたらもう終わるじゃん もう！
No, if we do that, it's game over!
なにそれ？ なにそれ？
What's that? What's that?
えー！ 2人がちょこの前でちゅうしてくれるなんて！
Wow! You two are going to kiss in front of me!
え、ちょこ先生にちゅうすんの。な、のら
No, we're kissing Choco-sensei. Nora.
あ、そういうことね！ 本当よかった マジで安心したわ今
Oh, I see! That's good. I'm so relieved now.
何を言い出したかと思って めちゃめちゃ焦ったわ今
I was so panicked thinking about what you were going to say.
ちょこ先生におめでとうのちゅうするのら
We'll give Choco-sensei a celebratory kiss.
なるほどね なるほど
I see, I see.
2人がちょこにちゅうしてくれるんだ！
So you two are going to kiss me!
しょうがねぇな 今日だけね 今日だけ
Can't be helped. Only for today, okay?
はい
Yes.
どっち？
Which side?
あ、おめでとうって
Saying congratulations...
ちょこ先生 ちゅう ちゅう ちゅう
Choco-sensei, kiss, kiss, kiss.
しょうがねぇな じゃあちょっと間失礼して
Can't be helped then. I'll just slip in between...
しょうがねぇなじゃねーよお前 何でお前がしょうがねぇな
Don't say "can't be helped"! Why are YOU saying it?
横どいて
Move aside.
何を言ってんだ！
What are you talking about!?
いやいやいや すいませんね もう
No, no, no. Sorry about that.
じゃあ 行きますよ
Okay, here we go.
お願い 監督お願いします
Please, Director, lead the way.
じゃあちょこ先生 5周年おめでちゅうの せーの！
Then, Choco-sensei, for your 5th anniversary... congratulations-chu! One, two...!
あー！ あー！ なにそれ！ あー！
Aaah! Aaah! What was that! Aaah!
それしてるやついるー！
Someone's actually doing it!
ルーナに吸い取られた！
I got sucked out by Luna!
わあー！
Whoa!
ちょっと何か妖怪いましたね今。
There was some kind of monster just now.
なんか...
Something like...
チョコ悪魔で吸う方なのになんか...
Choco is a demon, so she's the one who sucks, but...
逆に何かほっぺた伸びてるよ！
her cheek is stretching in reverse!
あ、ちょっとヨダレついちゃったかもな、な。
Ah, maybe a little drool got on it.
や、もうルーナたんのヨダレはご褒美だから。
Well, Luna-tan's drool is a reward.
汚ねえ！
That's gross!
じゃあね、この感じでね、元気になりましたか？
Anyway, feeling energized like this?
え、もう超元気になっちゃった。
Oh, I've become super energized.
よかった。
Glad to hear it.
よかったなのらー。
That's good, nora.
いやもうチョコ、今年も頑張れるわ。
Man, Choco can work hard again this year.
お、ごめん何これ。
Wait, sorry, what's this?
よかったよじゃあ。何降りじゃねえの。
That's good, then. What kind of vibe is this?
はい、ということで、この盛り上がった状態で次の曲行きましょう！
Alright, so let's move on to the next song in this hyped state!
チョコせんほっぺた光ってる。
Choco-sen's cheek is glowing.
どうぞ！
Here we go!
Crazy Party Night ～ぱんぷきんの逆襲～
Crazy Party Night ~Pumpkin's Revenge~
今日は 魔法の夜だから
Because tonight is a magical night
おかしな 世界に行こう
Let's go to a strange world
街に いたずら仕掛けて
Playing pranks on the town
とっても ワクワクするの
It's so very exciting
Ice cream, juice, foam, pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pam
夢の中に 迷い込んだみたい
It's like I've strayed into a dream
Ice cream, juice, foam, pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pam
ラララ ラララ みんなで踊ろうよ
La la la la la la, let's all dance together
パ・パ・ティ ピ・タ・パンキン
Pa-party, Pi-ta-pumpkin
ダンシン ダンシン ハロウィン
Dancin' dancin' Halloween
かわいい おばけと ハロ・ハロウィン
With cute ghosts, Hallo-Halloween
パ・パ・ティ ピ・タ・パンキン
Pa-party, Pi-ta-pumpkin
Crazy crazy crazy night
ダンシン ダンシン パンキン
Dancin' dancin' pumpkin
Crazy party night
パンパラパンパンパン パンパラパンクレイジーナイト
Pam-pa-ra-pam-pam-pam, Pam-pa-ra-pam crazy night
パンパラパンパンパン パンパラパンパーティナイト
Pam-pa-ra-pam-pam-pam, Pam-pa-ra-pam party night
夜空に 揺れる白い子たち
White children swaying in the night sky
トントンと 窓を灯す
Tap-tapping and lighting the windows
今夜 いたずら仕掛けて
Playing pranks tonight
街を カラフルに塗る
Painting the town in colors
Ice cream, juice, foam, pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pam
夢の中に 迷い込んだみたい
It's like I've strayed into a dream
Ice cream, juice, foam, pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pam
ラララ ラララ みんなで踊ろうよ
La la la la la la, let's all dance together
パ・パ・ティ ピ・タ・パンキン
Pa-party, Pi-ta-pumpkin
ダンシン ダンシン ハロウィン
Dancin' dancin' Halloween
かわいい おばけと ハロ・ハロウィン
With cute ghosts, Hallo-Halloween
パ・パ・ティ ピ・タ・パンキン
Pa-party, Pi-ta-pumpkin
Crazy crazy crazy night
ダンシン ダンシン パンキン
Dancin' dancin' pumpkin
Crazy party night
パ・パ・ティ ピ・タ・パンキン
Pa-party, Pi-ta-pumpkin
ダンシン ダンシン ハロウィン
Dancin' dancin' Halloween
かわいい おばけと ハロ・ハロウィン
With cute ghosts, Hallo-Halloween
パ・パ・ティ ピ・タ・パンキン
Pa-party, Pi-ta-pumpkin
Crazy crazy crazy night
ダンシン ダンシン パンキン
Dancin' dancin' pumpkin
Crazy party night
パ・パ・ティ ピ・タ・パンキン
Pa-party, Pi-ta-pumpkin
ダンシン ダンシン ハロウィン
Dancin' dancin' Halloween
かわいい おばけと ハロ・ハロウィン
With cute ghosts, Hallo-Halloween
パ・パ・ティ ピ・タ・パンキン
Pa-party, Pi-ta-pumpkin
Crazy crazy crazy night
ダンシン ダンシン パンキン
Dancin' dancin' pumpkin
Crazy party night
パ・パ・ティ ピ・タ・パンキン
Pa-party, Pi-ta-pumpkin
ダンシン ダンシン ハロウィン
Dancin' dancin' Halloween
かわいい おばけと ハロ・ハロウィン
With cute ghosts, Hallo-Halloween
パ・パ・ティ ピ・タ・パンキン
Pa-party, Pi-ta-pumpkin
Crazy crazy crazy night
ダンシン ダンシン パンキン
Dancin' dancin' pumpkin
Party night
ハロ ハロウィン
Hallo-Halloween
Crazy party night
ハロ ハロウィン
Hallo-Halloween
Crazy party night
扉開けたら まるでタイムマシン
When I open the door, it's just like a time machine
巻き戻された 夢のディスコティック
A rewound dream discotheque
君を捜して 怪しげなパーティー
Searching for you at a suspicious party
踊り明かす パンプキンのモンスター
Dancing the night away, pumpkin monsters
ミラーボールが回るダンスフロア
The mirror ball spins on the dance floor
仮装行列 誰かのミック・ジャガー
A costume parade, someone's Mick Jagger
僕は一人で 途方に暮れてる
I'm all alone, at a total loss
リズムの渦 どうすればいいの？
In a whirlpool of rhythm, what should I do?
ハロウィン・ナイト！ ミッドナイト！ 不気味なカボチャが誘ってる
Halloween night! Midnight! Spooky pumpkins are inviting us
さあ 手を叩け！ 腰を振れ！ 今夜は誰も馬鹿になれ！
Come on, clap your hands! Shake your hips! Tonight, everyone let loose!
ハロウィン・ナイト！ さあ 踊れ！ 言葉はいらないよ
Halloween night! Now, dance! No words are needed
もう 嫌なこと 忘れよう 年に一度のカーニバル
Let's forget the bad things, the once-a-year carnival
今日だけ自由な お化けたち ハロウィン・ナイト
Ghosts free for today only, Halloween night
なりたいものになれるファンタジー
A fantasy where you can be anything you want
願い叶えろ 一夜だけのマジック
Grant your wish, magic for one night only
大事なものは 子どもの頃の自分
What's important is the self from your childhood
本音のまま 生まれ変わるんだ
Reborn as your true self
ハロウィン・ナイト！ チェック・タイム！ 夜空が変わる前には
Halloween night! Check time! Before the night sky changes
さあ ステップを！ もう一度 出会いたいなら 目立つんだ！
Come on, take a step! If you want to meet again, stand out!
ハロウィン・ナイト！ さあ 踊れ！ 溢れる人の波
Halloween night! Now, dance! A wave of overflowing people
そう 理屈より 乗りで行け こんな世界の片隅で
Yes, go with the flow rather than logic, in a corner of this world
恋するメイク 特殊なスペシャル・ナイト
Lovestruck makeup, a special special night
Are you ready?
Ready?
Happy! Happy! Happy! Halloween night!
夜明けになって キスしているのは 僕たち二人だけ
At dawn, the ones kissing are only the two of us
愛はいつだって 強い引力
Love is always a strong attraction
H-A-L-L-O-W-E-E-N (1-2-3!)
ハロウィン・ナイト！ ミッドナイト！ 不気味なカボチャが誘ってる
Halloween night! Midnight! Spooky pumpkins are inviting us
さあ 手を叩け！ 腰を振れ！ 今夜は誰も馬鹿になれ！
Come on, clap your hands! Shake your hips! Tonight, everyone let loose!
ハロウィン・ナイト！ さあ 踊れ！ 言葉はいらないよ
Halloween night! Now, dance! No words are needed
もう 嫌なこと 忘れよう 年に一度のカーニバル
Let's forget the bad things, the once-a-year carnival
今日だけ自由な お化けたち ハロウィン・ナイト
Ghosts free for today only, Halloween night
Trick or Treat!
ゲストパート、皆様いかがだったでしょうかー！
How did you all enjoy the guest segment?!
今日はブラッククリスマスということで、
Since today is Black Christmas,
ちょっとね、ちょこからのプレゼントを、皆様に告知したいと思いまーす！
I'd like to announce some presents from Choco to everyone!
癒月ちょこ活動5周年記念グッズ、
Yuzuki Choco 5th Anniversary merchandise,
まずはこちら！
first up is this!
キャンバスアート
Canvas Art
ドドーン！さとうぽて先生描き下ろし、キャンバスアートー！
Ta-da! Canvas art newly illustrated by Sato Pote-sensei!
なんとね、こちら、ブラックサンタのちょこが、
So, this features Choco as Black Santa,
ちょっとね、まあ前からはね、えちえちかなあと思って、
and I thought showing her from the front might be a bit too sexy,
後ろ向きで皆様の方を見ているちょこでございます。
so here is Choco looking back at all of you.
まあこれだったらね、なんとちょこ先生えちすぎない、
Well, this way, Choco-sensei isn't too sexy,
皆様のお部屋にも飾れる素敵なキャンバスアートでございまーす！
it's a lovely canvas art that you can display in your room!
そしてお次はこちら！
And next is this!
ちょこ先生と契約の杯グラス
Chalice glass of contract with Choco-sensei
ちょこ先生と契約の杯グラス！
Chalice glass of contract with Choco-sensei!
ということでね、こちら。
So, here it is.
なんとこのね、グラスに、
If you pour some
まあイチゴミルクか何かね、注いでもらって、
strawberry milk or something into this glass
ちょこと一緒に乾杯したら、もう君は眷属だ！
and toast with Choco, you'll be one of my underlings!
さらにさらに、こちら！
Furthermore, this!
ちょこ♡ネックレス
Choco ♡ Necklace
なんと！こないだ発表した新衣装の
Behold! The necklace from
ちょこのネックレス、ハートのネックレスが
Choco's new outfit announced the other day,
なんと新グッズとなって登場だ！
the heart necklace is now available as a new item!
そして今回もあります、癒月ちょこ書き下ろしASMR台本！
And we have it again this time, an ASMR script written by Yuzuki Choco!
ということで、単品のボイスは2つでございます。
So, there are two individual voice packs.
記念ボイス
Memorial Voice
1つ目が、『ちょこサンタのお願い執着ASMR』ということでね。
The first one is 'Choco Santa's Obsessive Request ASMR.'
こちらは今年みんな良い子にしてたかな？
Did everyone behave themselves this year?
まあね、ということで、ちょこが本当に良い子なのか、
Well, Choco will see if you've really been a good child,
食診、いや、耳診？！していくボイスでございます。
with a medical checkup, no, an ear checkup?!
責められたい方はぜひ！
If you want to be scolded, this is for you!
そして2つ目は、『ツンデレサンタのご褒備ASMR』
And the second one is 'Tsundere Santa's Reward ASMR.'
ということで、聴き手の皆様はトナカイになった気分で 聴いていただけたら嬉しいです。
I'd be happy if listeners could enjoy it while feeling like a reindeer.
そしてフルセットはこちら！
And here's the full set!
フルセット購入特典
Full Set Purchase Bonus
ダダン、なんと購入特典が2種類あります！
Ta-da, there are two types of purchase bonuses!
まず1つ目は、今年もちゃんと書きます、
First, I'll be writing them properly again this year,
癒月ちょこ全部直筆サイン書きます！
I'll provide handwritten signatures on all of them!
プラス、箔押し複製メッセージ入り、 さとうぽて先生描き下ろしのポストカードでーす！
Plus, a postcard newly illustrated by Sato Pote-sensei with a foil-stamped message!
そして2つ目！お待たせしました、
And the second one! Sorry to keep you waiting,
溺愛ちょこの沼らせ意地悪ASMRボイスとなっております。
it's the 'Doting Choco's Sinking/Mean ASMR' voice pack.
こちらはね、ちょっとASMRボイス 僕ちょっとあんま聴いたことないよーって方に、
For those who haven't really listened to ASMR before,
初見さんぜひ、短めなので聴いて沼ってください。
for first-timers, it's short, so please listen and get hooked.
ということで、みんなちょこからのプレゼント、 ぜひぜひ手に入れてください！
So everyone, please make sure to get these presents from Choco!
活動5周年記念フルセット
5th Anniversary Memorial Full Set
そしてこの後はなんと、もう1つ ちょこからのプレゼントがあるのですが、
And after this, there's actually one more present from Choco,
その前に...
but before that...
うーん、恒例のやつやっちゃおうかな？
Hmm, should I do the usual thing?
レッドカーペット、召喚！
Red Carpet, summon!
はいということで、こちら毎年恒例のレッドカーペットを、 初めての方のためにご説明いたします。
Alright, let me explain this annual red carpet for the first-timers.
こちらのレッドカーペットなんと、 スーパーチャットを投げていただくと
This red carpet is designed to open up
プレゼントの方へ開いていく仕組みになっております。
towards the presents when you send Super Chats.
今年もよろしくお願いします！
Please support me again this year!
まあね、今回のグッズは、 ブラッククリスマス、テーマに...
Well, the merchandise this time is based on the Black Christmas theme...
色々と考えて作っております。
I've put a lot of thought into making this.
このね、ライブもブラッククリスマスをテーマに...
This live show's theme is Black Christmas...
見て見て、装飾とかも可愛いでしょ？
Look, look, the decorations are cute too, right?
あー、ありがとう！
Ah, thank you!
今年も可愛く作ってもらいましたー。
I had it made cute again this year too.
みんなありがとー！
Thank you everyone!
あともうちょっと、もうちょっと、もうちょっと。
Just a little more, a little more, a little more.
ありがとうー。
Thank you.
ということで、もう一つのプレゼントは...
And so, the other present is...
なんと新曲でーす！
Believe it or not, a new song!
聞いてください、「のーばでぃーくりすます」。
Please listen to "Nobody Christmas".
のーばでぃーくりすます！ 作詞・作曲・編曲：かめりあ
Nobody Christmas! Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Camellia
おどろおどろし季節
A spooky, eerie season
駆け足で過ぎ
Passing by in a hurry
純白も色変える
Even pure white changes color
真っ赤な聖なる季節
In this crimson holy season
悪夢にちょっと足して
Adding a bit to the nightmare
漆黒の雲に覆われる
Covered in jet-black clouds
雪降るツリーに
On the snowy tree
欲張りなお願いの山
A mountain of greedy wishes
欲しいって言われると
When told "I want it"
意地悪したくなっちゃうな
It makes me want to be mean
ちゃんと、おねだりして？
Make sure to... beg for it?
Nobody Christmas
悪い子にはご褒美なし
No rewards for bad children
サンタより悪魔がいいがね
Demons are better than Santa, aren't they?
願い叶えてあげる
I'll make your wish come true
また罠にかかった
Caught in a trap again
子羊さんウェルカム
Welcome, little lamb
罪深き邪悪な聖夜
A sinful, evil holy night
聖夜もゴーストも私のもの
The holy night and ghosts are mine too
もちろん、そこの君も
Of course, you there too
あれもこれもって
This and that too
目移りして困ってない？
Aren't you having trouble choosing?
そんな欲しいもの
Things you want so much
リスト消しておきました
I've removed them from the list
欲望、さらけ出して
Bare your desires
Nobody Christmas
ツリーの下にひっくり箱
An overturned box under the tree
驚いた表情は
Your surprised expression
ケーキよりデリシャスで
Is more delicious than cake
もっと見せて、その表情
Show me more of that expression
いい子なフリしてるだけでしょ
You're just pretending to be a good boy
昼夜逆転しちゃってるでしょ
Day and night are reversed, right?
プレゼントもいらないでしょ
You don't need presents, do you?
だって私がいれば満足でしょ
Because you're satisfied if I'm here, right?
靴下の中身、甘い誘惑
Inside the socks, sweet temptation
諦めておいで、Christmas for Nobody
Give up and come, Christmas for Nobody
Nobody Christmas
悪い子が夜更かししてる
A bad child is staying up late
クソガキ、凝りない
Shitty brat, doesn't learn
甘い甘いお仕置きで
With a sweet, sweet punishment
聖夜の前でいい子のフリ
Pretending to be a good child before the holy night
飴もらおうって魂胆なんて
Thinking you'll get candy with that scheme
甘いんですよ、ほら喜んで
It's so naive, look, be happy
今夜は帰さないわね
I won't let you go home tonight
Nobody Christmas
重大告知あり！
Major announcement!